(Sheldon:)Seriously?
(Sheldon:)He invented the Rubik's Cube.
(Penny:)Okay, fine,
(Penny:)but why would you invite him
to our wedding?
(Sheldon:)Because, despite his fame
and fortune,
(Sheldon:)he strikes me as a lonely man.
(Bernadette:)Well, it's very sweet
(Bernadette:)of you to go to all this trouble
for Leonard's mother.
(Penny:)Yeah, I'm also doing it
for Leonard.
(Penny:)I think this could really help
their relationship.
(Beverly:)How dare you invite your father
without consulting me!
(Leonard:)Sorry, but I don't think
I need your permission
(Leonard:)to have my father at my wedding.
(Beverly:)You do understand our marriage
ended because he had an affair.
(Leonard:)I know,
(Leonard:)and there's no excuse for that.
(Beverly:)He claimed I was cold,
emasculating,
(Beverly:)and hadn't shown him any
physical affection for years.
(Leonard:)I was wrong, there's
three excuses for that.
(Howard:)Oh, my God.
(Howard:)It's working.